Guide to the Rice University's University Relations Audio-Video records, 1962-2005 UA 126
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series VII: Interviews, 1997-2000, 149636
  - Carol Quillen Interview, Rice University (Tape 7 of 8) Beta T-30, 2 June 2000, 149644 (Box 11, Folder -)
  - James Baker Interview, Rice University (Tape 8 of 8) Beta T-30, 2 June 2000, 149645 (Box 11, Folder -)
  - Janice and Steven at 99 Park Ave. (Rice University), (Tape 1 of 2) Beta T-30, 15 June 2000, 149646 (Box 11, Folder -)
  - Janice and Steven at 99 Park Ave. (Rice University), (Tape 2 of 2) Beta T-30, 15 June 2000, 149647 (Box 11, Folder -)
  - Henry Wong Interview, Rice University (Tape 1 of 2) Beta T-30, 10 July 2000, 149648 (Box 12, Folder -)
  - Tevia Barnes Interview, Rice University (Tape 2 of 2) Beta T-30, 10 July 2000, 149649 (Box 12, Folder -)
  - Henry Wong and Tevia Barnes Interviews (Audio Cassette), c. 2000, 149650 (Box 12, Folder -)
  - Vicki Colvin Interview, Rice University (Tape 1 of 8 – Audio Cassette), 24 July 2000, 149651 (Box 12, Folder -)
  - Lisa Eshelman and Harsha Vaswani Interviews, Rice University (Tape 2 of 8 – Audio Cassette), 24 July 2000, 149652 (Box 12, Folder -)
  - Ric and Maribel Barrera Interview, Rice University (Tape 3 of 8 – Audio Cassette), 24 July 2000, 149653 (Box 12, Folder -)
  - Rick Stoll Interview, Rice University (Tape 4 of 8 – Audio Cassette), 25 July 2000, 149654 (Box 12, Folder -)
  - Rick Stoll Interview, Rice University (Tape 4 of 8 – Beta T-30), 25 July 2000, 149655 (Box 12, Folder -)
  - Cheryl Matheryly Interview, Rice University (Tape 5 of 8 – Audio Cassette), 25 July 2000, 149656 (Box 12, Folder -)
  - David Molina Interview, Rice University (Tape 6 of 8 – Audio Cassette), 25 July 2000, 149657 (Box 12, Folder -)
  - Corey Cogswell and Joanna Reese Interviews, Rice University (Tape 7 of 8 – Audio Cassette), 25 July 2000, 149658 (Box 12, Folder -)
  - Corey Cogswell and Joanna Reese Interviews, Rice University (Tape 7 of 8 – Beta T-30), 25 July 2000, 149659 (Box 12, Folder -)
  - Erik Haroze Interview, Rice University (Tape 8 of 8 – Audio Cassette), 26 July 2000, 149660 (Box 12, Folder -)
  - William Barnett Interview Tape #1, Beta T-30, 11 Sept 2000, 149661 (Box 12, Folder -)
  - Charles Duncan and Elias Bongmba (History) Interviews, Beta T-30, 149662 (Box 12, Folder -)
  - Dustin James, Tour Group Interview, Beta T-30, 149663 (Box 12, Folder -)
  - Isabel Interview, B-Roll, Rice Hall Cafeteria, Beta T-30, 149664 (Box 12, Folder -)
  - Kurt and Luke Interviews, Beta T-30, 149665 (Box 12, Folder -)
  - Lindsay Botsford, Class in Art Gallery Patio, Beta T-30, 149666 (Box 12, Folder -)
  - Malcolm Gillis Interview with Korean Television (Korean Format), 149667 (Box 12, Folder -)
  - Rice Interviews, 149668 (Box 12, Folder -)
  - William Martin and Gail Stokes Interviews, Beta T-30, 149669 (Box 12, Folder -)
  - Interview Transcripts: Dr. Boles, Elias Bongmba, James Baker, James Tour, Bucky Allshouse, Robert McNair, Lindsay Botsford, Luke, Kurt, Rick Stoll, Henry Wong, Charles Duncan, Carol Quillen, Teveia Barnes, Dr. Stokes, Charles Duncan, Malcolm Gillis, Isabella., 149670 (Box 12, Folder -)
- Series VIII: Houston Events and Promotional Media, 1993-2001, 149671
  - AVW Audio/Visual, Inc. Production Demo, Fall 1993, 149672 (Box 13, Folder -)
  - "Houston: The Real Texas" TRT: 5 min 32 sec, 1994, 149673 (Box 13, Folder -)
  - HISD Media Television Services "Parallel Juggler" TRT: 18 min 43 sec, 18 Oct 1995, 149674 (Box 13, Folder -)
  - Exxon Company "Summer Chills", Alley Theatre Series 97, TRT: 33 sec, 30 June 1997, 149675 (Box 13, Folder -)
  - "In Houston Living is Good", Houston Lighting and Power, TRT: 10 min 54 sec, 1997, 149676 (Box 13, Folder -)
  - HISD/OPA, April 1999, 149677 (Box 13, Folder -)
  - Greater Houston Convention & Visitors Bureau; Generic Version (no people)/ Revised Aeros Audio TRT: 9 minutes 59 sec, 1999, 149678 (Box 13, Folder -)
  - Nion Interactive Opportunity Houston, 27 Sept 2001, 149679 (Box 13, Folder -)
  - Houston Stock Footage, Beta T-30, 149680 (Box 13, Folder -)
  - Opportunity Houston, Granite House, Beta SP T-10, 149681 (Box 13, Folder -)
  - University World Science Partners for Houston Produced by U.T. System TRT: 5 min, 149682 (Box 13, Folder -)
  - Space Center Houston (Tape 1 and 2), 149683 (Box 13, Folder -)
  - Space Center Houston (Video 1 of 2), 149684 (Box 13, Folder -)
  - Space Center Houston (Video 2 of 2), 149685 (Box 13, Folder -)
  - Space Center Houston: Electronic Press Kit TRT: 23 min 32 sec (2 Copies), 149686 (Box 13, Folder -)
  - "The Power of a Dream", Texas Medical Center TRT: 6 min, 149687 (Box 13, Folder -)
  - "This is Houston" Official Newcomer Video of Greater Houston Partnership, 149688 (Box 13, Folder -)